{
    "subject": "resource/Plaid_Cymru",
    "predicate": "property/ideology",
    "object": "resource/Social_democracy",
    "human_readable": "The ideology of Plaid Cymru is Social democracy.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8889895677566528,
            "question": "What is the ideology of Plaid Cymru?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8116686940193176,
            "question": "How does Plaid Cymru's ideology align with traditional democratic values?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7746910452842712,
            "question": "How has Plaid Cymru's ideology influenced its political platform?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.769995927810669,
            "question": "What role does social justice play in Plaid Cymru's ideology?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.64759761095047,
            "question": "What type of democracy does Plaid Cymru support?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5952993035316467,
            "question": "Do you think Plaid Cymru's ideology is popular among the Welsh population?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2980623245239258,
            "question": "Describe the core beliefs of Social Democracy."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2261040359735489,
            "question": "What are some key differences between Social Democracy and other political ideologies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20661978423595428,
            "question": "Can you provide examples of policies commonly associated with Social Democracy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19703784584999084,
            "question": "What are some potential challenges facing a party that adheres to Social Democracy?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The ideology of Plaid Cymru is Social democracy.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5924_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide examples of policies commonly associated with Social Democracy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5924_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some key differences between Social Democracy and other political ideologies?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5924_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Describe the core beliefs of Social Democracy.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5924_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5924_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5924_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5924_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5924_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5924_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5924_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5924_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5924_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5924_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5924_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation in the requested JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the documents contain information about Alan Sandry's book \"Plaid Cymru: An Ideological Analysis\", which challenges some perceptions surrounding the party's ideology and asserts that Plaid Cymru is more of a socialist party, albeit with a complex matrix of underlying ideologies. This suggests that the ideology of Plaid Cymru includes social democracy."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that Plaid Cymru's predominant ideological stance has been described as modernist, which includes a mixture of cultural conservatism and innovative social democracy. Therefore, it supports the statement that The ideology of Plaid Cymru is Social democracy."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}